Dâmocles Gil Marçal

Senior Front-end Engineer

EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-end Engineer

Calculato

Nov 2019 - Present - 5 years 1 mos, Brazil

I worked on the development team as a front-end engineer of web projects. I used all my software architecture knowledge to improve the performance, maintainability, scalability, and readability of the projects. I also use my development skills with the best customer experience in mind, with disruptive and value-generating solutions. Stacks: Vue.js, GRAPHQL, Tailwindcss, Typescript and Next.js

Front-end Engineer

NectarCRM

Sep 2019 - Nov 2019 - 2 mos, Brazil

I worked on the development team as Front-End on the core project (NectarCRM) using the angularjs framework.

Full-stack developer

Daxplace

Apr 2018 - Sep 2019 - 1 year 5 mos, Brazil

In Daxplace I used Vue in the Front-end, and Node.js, Laravel in the Back-end. Still, in the Daxplace Four, I had a bigger challenge, constructing a crypto system. Yes, here I learned a lot about people and how they work.

Web Designer

Conexão Soluções Corporativas

Jan 20218 - Apr 2018 - 3 mos, Brazil

Development of new features to the site, backstage administration and other stuff for the product. Help to create the best UX/UI, using HTML5, CSS, JS, JQUERY, PHP and more.

Web Developer

Actuar Sistemas

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017 - 11 Mos, Brazil

In this company I worked on many fronts, from developing email marketing, setting up google adwords, creating and maintaining websites and web applications.

EDUCATION

Information Technology Management

SENAC - Technology University

2015 - 2018, Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

Web Designer - Technical Course

MCTech Courses - Specialized apple

2014 - 2016, Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil



damoclesgil@gmail.com +55 62 98116-5159

About me

I'm 27 years old, I'm live in Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil, I'm a senior front-end engineer. I've been working in the area for 9 yrs.

I have a strong background in web design, user interface, and user experience. I am passionate about creating engaging, responsive, and accessible web pages.

Skills

Vue.js, Next.js, Jest, Typescript, GraphQL.

Languages

Português - Brazil (native) English (advanced)

Social

https://damoclesgil.com.br/
lim linkedin.com/in/damoclesgil
github.com/damoclesgil